Oh, there's like a plant.
I just wanted to go on here
because I need y'all to know something.
I have never made a video and been like,
yeah, they gonna post this.
They gonna post this.
So every time that they do that,
I'm always like, oh, wow.
Because I really just be,
I just really be here with the phone.
Maybe it's because I'm an only child or something,
but I really just be here with the phone
and I'll just say something and I'll just move on.
And so I really be shocked when it's like,
this is a thing.
So imagine my surprise.
Nonetheless, I just wanted to clarify something
because I feel like this poster,
I mean, this post that I made about,
you know, not being invited into black spaces,
the real thing that I wanted
to be received from that was that
it's y'all that matter.
It's y'all that matter.
Like that's what I really wanted to be received from that.
And I guess my delivery
did not do that effectively.
But that was really the point of my video.
It was to say, thank you all.
And I meant that in a very literal way.
Like, thank you all.
Because it really is an awakening
when you come to understand that,
oh, it's the people on the ground.
Like it's the people that see you and say like,
yo, keep going.
It's the people that leave hearts here.
You know, it's the people.
Like that's really what is the most important thing.
And for so many creatives,
we don't understand that
because we have been so pulled into this like idea
that we got to be trying to please these people
that you get caught up in like trying to please those people
not really understanding.
Like, they not it.
It's us.
It's y'all.
Like they not it, you know?
And so that's really what I was trying to get across.
And I know like some people are like,
well, I don't understand.
It's like, you don't care what people think,
but you want to be invited in their spaces.
And it's like, well, two things can be true
at the same time, right?
Like you can simultaneously be like,
I need to do what needs to be done.
I need to say what needs to be said.
While also really feeling like, damn,
it's unfortunate that these spaces that benefit
from that type of ardent challenging of systems
that oppress it,
it's unfortunate that those places don't like,
shut up, Michael,
that those places don't see like the value
in what you do to enhance those spaces.
So I don't know.
I'll speak more to this tonight.
On the small doses bonus episode,
you can subscribe to my Patreon
and you can get our weekly small bonus episodes
where I really, I keep it very, very real.
Even realer than I do here.
But I just wanted to,
why am I yelling?
I just be yelling.
I be like, that's the other thing.
Y'all be like, she's always yelling.
It's like, cause I talk loud.
Like I'm a loud talker.
Like I just talk loud.
Even my nipples are loud right now.
Like I just, I'm loud.
Anywho.
So I just wanted to elucidate that.
Ooh, that was a good one for a Sunday.
I just wanted to elucidate that.
Because I feel like it's important to me
that y'all know that that message was about y'all.
That message was about y'all.
And father, father of,
oh, your name is already gone.
But he said, it's an only child thing.
You know, I think there's something very real
about wanting to be understood
and accepted in spaces that you are protecting.
And I think that that's really, you know, important.
I love black people.
I love our culture.
I feel like there is a constant attack
on our culture, et cetera.
And so I do my best to inform and educate and whatnot.
And, you know, I don't think there's anything crazy
for wanting like to not be left out
of the celebratory spaces of those spaces.
Jordi, you know, you don't have to go outside.
You know, you don't have to go outside.
I'm coming.
Come here.
Um, yeah.
So anywho, uh, I just wanted to share that
and thank you all for, uh, again,
showing me love.
Hey, Anthony Dickey.
Thank you.
And, uh, I did a, I did a YouTube live last night
where we talked about Sean King.
We talked about, um, the TikTok ban.
We talked about Cop City.
We talked about Trump using language like bloodbath.
I mean, I think it was a really, really great, um, conversation
that I was having with the chat, et cetera.
So make sure you check that out on YouTube and subscribe.
And again, um, of course loud can come off as aggressive.
Like everything is subjective.
Everything is subjective.
I could be talking like this and someone thinks I'm yelling at them.
Even if I'm like, happy birthday.
I think you're awesome.
Perfect example.
I was on a flight the other day and the flight attendant literally said,
the bathrooms are now closed down.
If you need to go to the bathroom, then you need to wait until we take off.
Until we're at 10,000 feet.
Okay.
30,000 feet.
Sorry.
10,000, 30,000, whatever.
She said, the bathrooms are closed.
Two seconds later, a clear woman rises and walks to the bathroom.
Now I was holding mine cause she had just said the bathroom was closed down.
So I was holding mine, but then I see this one come through and I'm like, what is we doing?
So now I get up and I go and the woman is in the bathroom.
And so the flight attendant is standing there and I was like, like scared her because it
was like, she heard my, she heard my, I don't know.
She just, I don't know.
She just misconstrued my energy.
I was, I was like trying to relate to her, but she read it as I'm trying to come for her.
That's perception.
Perception is your personal reality.
You cannot control other people's perception.
So the woman was like, the flight attendant was like, um, well, you seem very insistent.
So if you want to go, like you can go.
And I was like, oh no, I'm not insistent.
I'm just a passionate person.
And I'm just telling you, like, I, like I heard what you said and I thought it was kind
of wild that, that she would be there.
And I was holding mine cause of what you just said.
And she was like, oh, well, I mean, I'm not trying to, um, control what people do.
And I was like, oh, but you just said that we can't go to the bathroom.
And she was like, yeah, but I can't, I can't stop people from going to the bathroom.
Like, that's just what the thing says that I'm supposed to read.
And I was like, oh, okay.
Or, you know, but that's a, that's a perfect example.
Okay.
So here's this miss cute face thick in the waist.
Do you think my mother is white?
Why are we here in 2024?
And y'all still think I have a white parent?
Not that there's anything wrong with that, but it's just not the case.
And you only say it to try to disparage me.
The only time y'all say that is to try to disparage me.
The only time.
I do not have a white parent.
I have two black parents.
Two.
Yes.
One from Roxbury, Boston.
One from the island of my parents.
I just, I don't, for so Twitter since 2008.
I've been on Instagram since 2008.
Anywho.
So that was my, all I was saying was that's a, that flight attendant story was an example.
Yes.
Roxbury.
Roxbury, Boston in the fifties and sixties.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I just got my genealogy done.
And so we're going to do an episode of my podcast, Small Doses, that will be like my finding your roots.
Excited.
So, yeah.
I just, um, that was weird.
Anywho.
So I just, I just wanted to, uh, tell y'all that, uh, you know, perception is reality.
And he says, someone is behind me.
Jordy is behind me because Jordy wants to go outside, but he's going to go outside and then he's going to turn around because he wants to play.
But I need to eat something first.
And we're about to play in a little bit because I'm going to play tennis.
So I'm just like, if you would just be patient for a little bit, you know, then now watch, watch.
Y'all saw that, right?
Yes.
I'm the one who does Black Yard News.
On the Amanda Seals show.
Y'all saw that, right?
Y'all saw him make me come and open the door.
And then walk right back in, right?
Y'all saw it?
Come here.
Okay.
Just, just making sure y'all saw that.
Um, yes, I am on 100.3 WRMB.
I am the morning show in Philadelphia every day, Monday through Friday, the Amanda Seals show.
Check me out with my co-hosts, DJ Supreme and TJ.
It's a great time.
This week I was out.
I took a mental health week.
So there's that.
No, I know he wants me to go out there and play, but I got to eat something right now.
And we're going to play in a very short amount of time.
But it's like, bruh, I need you to just, I need you to just pause it for a minute.
Um, thank you, Kissed by Melanin.
Thank you, Farrell.
We up.
Amanda Seals, y'all.
Yes.
Okay.
I will bring back the Smartphone in Black tour, but I needed a break.
I needed a break.
Actually, speaking of Boston, my tickets for Boston go on sale.
They're up on my link tree.
Someone just asked when I'm coming to Dallas.
I'm going to Fort Worth on April 12th through the 14th.
April 12th to the 14th.
He's not on the show anymore.
That's what happened to him.
April 12th to the 14th.
Um, I'm not doing any shows in LA.
I'm reading your comments real quick.
I'm looking at Houston right now.
I'm not bringing Smartphone in Black.
I'm not doing Smartphone in Black this year.
Um, okay.
There you go.
So that's that.
Like I said, check out, uh, Small Doses podcast.
We do bonus episodes every Sunday at 7.30 p.m.
If you are a Patreon member, you can listen and you can also join me in the live recording.
So go to, um, yeah.
Go to Patreon Amanda Seals.
Thank you.
I'm glad you enjoyed yourself in San Diego.
And again, for all the people who are, who were here, who was on the YouTube live last
night for the Common Sense Kickback, make sure that you check that out.
A lot of good information.
I love that the comment section be just as much, just as informative as, you know, the
information I'm bringing.
Cause that's what we need.
We need a community of intellectualism.
All right.
Bye y'all.